



Oussama Harrathi

Nationality: Tunisian | **Phone number:** (+36) 305136642 (Mobile) |

Email address: oussamaharrathi333@gmail.com | LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/oussama-harrathi-a049b2195/

Address: szigeti utca, 7624, pécs, Hungary (Home)

ABOUT ME

After completing my studies in Computer Science Engineering at the University of Pécs, I have acquired practical knowledge in JavaScript, TypeScript, Java, and C# through various projects and internships in software development. I am dedicated to ongoing growth and I am excited to apply my expertise to drive meaningful success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/06/2023 - 31/08/2023 Kairouan, Tunisia

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN SORETRAK TUNISIA

- Developed a web app for employees within the company using angular, NodeJs, ExpressJs and Oracle database to enter their sons data who are eligible for scholarship making the operation easier, and an admin app to help him control the operation.
- Collaborated with a team of software engineers to design and develop efficient software solutions.

01/10/2022 - 28/02/2023 Debrecen, Hungary

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE TRANSOSMOS HUNGARY

Provided assistance to customers on phones calls, emails and chats

31/12/2018 - 11/05/2020 kairouan, Tunisia

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER SORETRAK

- Used Angular to develop and maintain web applications for optimal speed, responsiveness, and scalability.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to design and implement solutions aligned with project requirements.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

05/09/2020 - 31/01/2024 Pecs, Hungary

BACHELOR FOR COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEERING University of Pécs, Hungary

Website mik.pte.hu

15/09/2017 - 30/06/2018 Kairouan, Tunisia

BACCALAUREATE IN MATHEMATICS Pioneer High school Kairouan

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ARABIC**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
FRENCH	B2	B2	B1	B1	B2
ENGLISH	B2	B2	B2	B2	B2
ENGLISH	B2	B2	B2	B2	B2
GERMAN	A1	A1	A1	A1	A1
HUNGARIAN	A1	A1	A1	A1	A1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Soft Skills

Good listener and communicator | Written and Verbal skills | Team-work oriented | Motivated | Adaptability | continuous learning | Critical Thinking.

Technical skills

Angular | TypeScript | Javascript(Nodejs) | SQL(Oracle DB) | HTML/CSS | Basic git | C# | Java